A Guide to the Harry F. Byrd Jr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Legislative Files
  - President: Executive Privilege, 1973 (Box Box 408)
  - President: Former Presidents, 1972-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 408)
  - President: Inauguration, 1972-1973 (Box Box 408)
  - President: Inherent Powers, 1973-1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 408)
  - President: Leadership, 1973-1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 409)
  - President: Pension Freeze of Federal Employees, 1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 409)
  - President: Pensions of Former Presidents, 1981-1982 (Box Box 409)
  - President: Reorganization, 1977 (Box Box 409)
  - President: Requests from Constituents, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 409)
  - President: San Clemente Expenses, 1973-1974 (Box Box 409)
  - President: Six Year Term Proposal, 1973-1974 (Box Box 409)
  - President: State of the Union Message, 1975; (3 folders) (Box Box 410)
  - President: Tax Proposals, 1975, 1978 (Box Box 410)
  - President: Vice-President, 1973, 1974 November-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 410)
  - President: Vice-President, 1974 January-October, 1975; (8 folders) (Box Box 411)
  - President: Vice-President Residence, 1974 (Box Box 411)
  - President: Vice-President (Special Folder), 1973-1981 (Box Box 411)
  - Prisons, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 412)
  - Prisons: Apple Orchard Mountain, 1976 (Box Box 412)
  - Science, 1973-1981 (Box Box 412)
  - Science: Research, 1973-1975; (4 folders) (Box Box 412)
  - Science: Research, 1976-1981; (3 folders) (Box Box 413)
  - Science: Research - Animals, 1973-1974, 1975 June-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 413)
  - Science: Research - Animals, 1975 January-May, 1976-1982; (9 folders) (Box Box 414)
  - Science: Research - Space and Aeronautics, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 415)
  - Security, 1973-1977 (Box Box 415)
  - Taxes, 1973-1978; (5 folders) (Box Box 415)
  - Taxes, 1979 April-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 416)
  - Taxes, 1979 January-March, 1980 September-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 417)
  - Taxes, 1980 May 21-30, June-August; (7 folders) (Box Box 418)
  - Taxes, 1980 January-May 16, 1981 April-November; (7 folders) (Box Box 419)
  - Taxes, 1981 January-March, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 420)
  - Taxes: Business Credits, 1977 (Box Box 420)
  - Taxes: Capital Gains, 1977, 1978 July-October; (4 folders) (Box Box 420)
  - Taxes: Capital Gains, 1978 January-June, 1979-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 421)
  - Taxes: Carryover, 1976-1978, 1979 April-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 421)
  - Taxes: Carryover, 1979 January-March, 1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 422)
  - Taxes: Charitable Contributions, 1972-1973, 1974 April-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 422)
  - Taxes: Charitable Contributions, 1974 January-March, 1975 May-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 423)
  - Taxes: Charitable Contributions, 1975 January-April, 1976-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 424)
  - Taxes: Charitable Foundations - Exemption, 1977-1978 (Box Box 424)
  - Taxes: Contractors, 1981-1982 (Box Box 424)
  - Taxes: Corporate, 1977-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 424)
  - Taxes: Credit for the Elderly, 1977 (Box Box 424)
  - Taxes: Credit for Elderly, 1978-1979 (Box Box 425)
  - Taxes: Depreciation, 1981 (Box Box 425)
  - Taxes: Economic Stimulus Proposal, 1977 (Box Box 425)
  - Taxes: Education, 1972-1977; (5 folders) (Box Box 425)
  - Taxes: Education, 1978; (7 folders) (Box Box 426)
  - Taxes: Education, 1979-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 427)
  - Taxes: Education, 1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 428)
  - Taxes: ERISA, 1977-1982 (Box Box 428)
  - Taxes: Estate, 1973-1980; (4 folders) (Box Box 428)
  - Taxes: Estate, 1981-1982 (Box Box 429)
  - Taxes: Excise, 1973-1982 (Box Box 429)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1972-1973; (4 folders) (Box Box 429)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1974 August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 430)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1974 January-July; (9 folders) (Box Box 431)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1975 August-December; (8 folders) (Box Box 432)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1975 March 24-July; (8 folders) (Box Box 433)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1975 January-March 22; (8 folders) (Box Box 434)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1976 July-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 435)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1976 May 11-31, June; (7 folders) (Box Box 436)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1976 March-April, May 1-10; (7 folders) (Box Box 437)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1976 January-February, 1977; (6 folders) (Box Box 438)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1978 July-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 439)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1978 March 16-31, April-June; (7 folders) (Box Box 440)
  - Taxes: Federal Reform, 1978 January-March 1-15, 1979; (4 folders) (Box Box 441)
  - Taxes: Federal Retirees, 1977 (Box Box 441)
  - Taxes: Gasoline, 1974-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 441)
  - Taxes: Income, 1972-1977; (4 folders) (Box Box 442)
  - Taxes: Income Earned Abroad, 1975-1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 442)
  - Taxes: Income Earned Abroad, 1979-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 443)
  - Taxes: Interest Equalization, 1973-1982 (Box Box 443)
  - Taxes: IRS, 1973-1976; (3 folders) (Box Box 443)
  - Taxes: IRS, 1977-1979; (5 folders) (Box Box 444)
  - Taxes: IRS, 1980, 1981 June-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 445)
  - Taxes: IRS, 1981 January-May, 1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 446)
  - Taxes: Interstate, 1973-1974 (Box Box 446)
  - Taxes: Investment Credit, 1973-1980, 1981 June-November; (2 folders) (Box Box 446)
  - Taxes: Investment Credit, 1981 January-May, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 447)
  - Taxes: Job Credits, 1980-1981 (Box Box 447)
  - Taxes: Miscellaneous, 1977-1980, 1981 September-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 447)
  - Taxes: Miscellaneous, 1981 January-August; (7 folders) (Box Box 448)
  - Taxes: Miscellaneous, 1982 July 26-31, August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 449)
  - Taxes: Miscellaneous, 1982 June-July 1-23; (7 folders) (Box Box 450)
  - Taxes: Miscellaneous, 1982 March 23-31, April-May; (6 folders) (Box Box 451)
  - Taxes: Miscellaneous, 1982 January-March 1-22; (2 folders) (Box Box 452)
  - Taxes: Mortgages, 1981-1982 (Box Box 452)
  - Taxes: Pensions, 1973-1979, 1980 July-December; (3 folders) (Box Box 452)
  - Taxes: Pensions, 1980 January-June, 1981-1982; (5 folders) (Box Box 453)
  - Taxes: Personal Exemptions, 1973-1981; (4 folders) (Box Box 454)
  - Taxes: Revenue Sharing, 1971-1973; (4 folders) (Box Box 454)
  - Taxes: Revenue Sharing, 1974-1976; (7 folders) (Box Box 455)
  - Taxes: Revenue Sharing, 1977-1982; (7 folders) (Box Box 456)
  - Taxes: Savings, 1981 (Box Box 456)
  - Taxes: Sick Pay, 1977-1982 (Box Box 456)
  - Taxes: Small Business, 1981-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 457)
  - Taxes: State, 1971-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 457)
  - Taxes: Tax Rebate, 1977 (Box Box 457)
  - Taxes: Tax Treaties, 1977-1978 (Box Box 457)
  - Taxes: Truck Deregulation, 1981 (Box Box 457)
  - Taxes: Wheat Sales, 1973 (Box Box 457)
  - Taxes: World Peace Fund, 1977-1982 (Box Box 457)
  - United Nations, 1972-1978; (7 folders) (Box Box 458)
  - United Nations, 1979-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 459)
  - Veterans, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 459)
  - Veterans: Benefits, 1973 March 16-30, April-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 459)
  - Veterans: Benefits, 1973 January-March 1-15, 1974; (8 folders) (Box Box 460)
  - Veterans: Benefits, 1975-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 461)
  - Veterans: Cemeteries, 1973-1978 (Box Box 461)
  - Veterans: Education, 1976-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 461)
  - Veterans: Hospitals and Healthcare, 1973-1980 (Box Box 462)
  - Veterans: Legislation, 1973-1977; (6 folders) (Box Box 462)
  - Veterans: Legislation, 1978-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 463)
  - Veterans: Pensions, 1976-1979 (Box Box 463)
  - Virginia Affairs, 1973-1975, 1976 May-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 463)
  - Virginia Affairs, 1976 January-April, 1977-1979; (6 folders) (Box Box 464)
  - Virginia Affairs, 1980-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 465)
  - Virginia Affairs: Agriculture, 1974-1978 (Box Box 465)
  - Virginia Affairs: Alcohol Beverage Control Board, 1973-1979 (Box Box 465)
  - Virginia Affairs: Alcohol Beverage Control Board, 1980-1982 (Box Box 466)
  - Virginia Affairs: Army Corp of Engineers, 1973-1974, 1975 June-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 466)
  - Virginia Affairs: Army Corp of Engineers, 1975 January-May, 1976-1978; (7 folders) (Box Box 467)
  - Virginia Affairs: Army Corp of Engineers, 1979-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 468)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government, 1973-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 468)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government - Alexandria Waterfront Dispute, 1971-1974 (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government - Alleghany County, Fairfax County, Hampton & Manassas, 1977-1981 (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government - Hybla Valley, 1973-1979 (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government - Newport News, 1979-1980 (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government - Upper Occoquan & Virginia Beach, 1978-1979 (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: City and County Government - Warsaw (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: Conservation and Economic Development Commission, 1976-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 469)
  - Virginia Affairs: Coors Controversy, 1979-1981 (Box Box 470)
  - Virginia Affairs: Corrections, Dept. of, 1977-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 470)
  - Virginia Affairs: Division of Motor Vehicles, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 470)
  - Virginia Affairs: Employment Commission, 1976-1982 (Box Box 470)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection, 1973-1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 470)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection, 1975-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 471)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Air & Water Pollution, 1973-1982 (Box Box 471)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities, 1973-1976; (4 folders) (Box Box 471)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities, 1977-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 472)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities (Alleghany County & Blue Plains), 1973-1975 (Box Box 472)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities (Cypress Creek Bridge, Danville, Fairfax County), 1973-1974 (Box Box 472)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities (Frederick County & Hopewell), 1973-1974 (Box Box 472)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities (Hampton Roads), 1973, 1975-1976 (Box Box 473)
  - Virginia Affairs: Environmental Protection - Water & Sewage Facilities (Ivy Creek, Portsmouth, Potomac River Basin, Upper Occoquan, Virginia Beach & Warsaw), 1973-1977 (Box Box 473)
  - Virginia Affairs: Game & Fish Management, 1973-1979 (Box Box 473)
  - Virginia Affairs: General Assembly, 1973-1980; (6 folders) (Box Box 473)
  - Virginia Affairs: General Assembly, 1981-1982 (Box Box 474)
  - Virginia Affairs: Grants, 1977-1982 (Box Box 474)
  - Virginia Affairs: Health, 1973-1982; (6 folders) (Box Box 474)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways, 1973-1982; (8 folders) (Box Box 475)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways, Commission On, 1974-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 476)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways - Dulles Access Road, 1973-1978 (Box Box 476)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways - Elizabeth Bridge Tunnel, 1975 (Box Box 476)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways - I-66, 1973-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 476)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways - I-77, 1973-1976 (Box Box 477)
  - Virginia Affairs: Highways - I-95, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 477)
  - Virginia Affairs: Historic Preservation, 1973-1974; (5 folders) (Box Box 477)
  - Virginia Affairs: Historic Preservation, 1975-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 478)
  - Virginia Affairs: Housing, 1974-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 479)
  - Virginia Affairs: Housing - Fairfax County, 1973-1981 (Box Box 479)
  - Virginia Affairs: Housing - Floods, 1977-1979 (Box Box 479)
  - Virginia Affairs: Housing - Hurricane Agnes, 1972-1975 (Box Box 479)
  - Virginia Affairs: Industrial Development, 1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 479)
  - Virginia Affairs: Industrial Development, 1974-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: National Credit Union Administration, 1976-1981 (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: National Guard Units, 1975 (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: Officials, 1973-1979 (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: Officials - Attorney General, 1973-1982 (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: Officials - Governor, 1974-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: Officials - Lt. Governor, 1979-1981 (Box Box 480)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation, 1973-1976; (7 folders) (Box Box 481)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation, 1977-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 482)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Appalachian Trail, 1973-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 482)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Appomattox Court House, 1973-1978 (Box Box 482)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Assateague, 1973-1979; (2 folders) (Box Box 482)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Back Bay National Wildlife, 1971-1981; (4 folders) (Box Box 483)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Blue Ridge Parkway, 1973-1981 (Box Box 483)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Bull Run Mountain, 1973 (Box Box 483)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Colonial National Historical Park, 1973, 1977 (Box Box 483)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Dismal Swamp, 1968-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 483)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Dismal Swamp, 1974-1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Eastern Shore, 1971-1973 (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Fairfax County Park Authority, 1976, n.d. (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Ferry Farm, 1971-1974 (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Fredericksburg, 1976 (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Front Royal Zoo Annex, 1973-1974 (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - George Washington National Forest, 1973-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Groundhog Mountain, 1976, 1978 (Box Box 484)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Jefferson National Forest, 1972-1976; (2 folders) (Box Box 485)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Kananwha Canal Project, 1972-1973 (Box Box 485)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Manassas National Battlefield, 1973, 1976-1978 July-October; (4 folders) (Box Box 485)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Manassas National Battlefield, 1978 January-June, 1979-81, n.d.; (6 folders) (Box Box 486)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Piscataway National Park, 1973 May 18-August (Box Box 486)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Piscataway National Park, 1973 February-May 11, 1974; (4 folders) (Box Box 487)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Potomac Heritage Trail, 1974-1977 (Box Box 487)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Shenandoah National Park, 1973 (Box Box 487)
  - Virginia Affairs: Parks & Recreation - Shenandoah National Park, 1974-1978 & 1980; (7 folders) (Box Box 488)
  - Virginia Affairs: Powhatan Confederation, 1972-1973, 1976 (Box Box 488)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works, 1973-1976; (6 folders) (Box Box 489)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works, 1977-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 490)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Back Creek Dam, 1976 (Box Box 490)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Bath County Dam, 1974-1976 (Box Box 490)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Blue Ridge Dam, 1967-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 490)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Blue Ridge Dam, 1974-1976; (4 folders) (Box Box 491)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Buena Vista, 1972-1977; (2 folders) (Box Box 491)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Catoctin Creek, 1974-1975 (Box Box 491)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel, 1974-1979 (Box Box 491)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Clinchport, 1973, 1977-1978 (Box Box 491)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Contrary Creek Demonstration Project (Louisa County), 1974 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Dry Riverbed Clearance, 1972-1973 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Four Mile Run, 1972-1974 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Gathright Dam, 1973-1978; (3 folders) (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Hampton Roads, 1973-1974 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Hipes Dam, 1973 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - James River, 1973-1980 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - John H. Kerr Dam & Reservoir, 1976 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Louisa County, 1973 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Naked Creek, 1972 (Box Box 492)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - New River, 1973-1975, 1976 August-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 493)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - New River, 1976 January-July, 1977-1979; (4 folders) (Box Box 494)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Nibbs Creek, 1976-1978; (2 folders) (Box Box 494)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Regional Planning Commission, 1973-1974 (Box Box 494)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Roanoke River Basin, 1973-1974 (Box Box 494)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Salem Church Dam & Reservoir, 1973-1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 494)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Slate Creek, Buchanan County, 1972 (Box Box 495)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Southampton County Water & Sewer, 1973-1974 (Box Box 495)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Verona Dam, 1973-1977; (3 folders) (Box Box 495)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - Virginia Beach Erosion, 1973 (Box Box 495)
  - Virginia Affairs: Public Works - York & Pamunkey Rivers, 1973 (Box Box 495)
  - Virginia Affairs: Schools, 1973-1979; (3 folders) (Box Box 495)
  - Virginia Affairs: Schools, 1980-1982 (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: Schools - Portsmouth Public Schools, 1971-1972 (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: Schools - University of Virginia, 1973-1981 (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: Schools - Virginia Military Institute, 1973-1981 (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: Schools - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: State Bar Examination Board, 1978 & 1982 (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: Taxation, 1973-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 496)
  - Virginia Affairs: Utilities, 1975-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 497)
  - Virginia Affairs: Utilities - VEPCO, 1973-1974, 1975 May-December; (5 folders) (Box Box 497)
  - Virginia Affairs: Utilities - VEPCO, 1975 January-April, 1976-1981; (7 folders) (Box Box 498)
  - Virginia Affairs: Virginia Port Authority, 1972-1976 (Box Box 499)
  - Virginia Affairs: Virginia Procurement Conference, 1974-1976 (Box Box 499)
  - Virginia Affairs: Voting, 1973-1980 (Box Box 499)
  - Virginia Affairs: Welfare, 1974-1981 (Box Box 499)
  - Watergate, 1973 October 29-31, November-December; (4 folders) (Box Box 499)
  - Watergate, 1973 May-September, October 1-26; (7 folders) (Box Box 500)
  - Watergate, 1973 March-April, 1974; (8 folders) (Box Box 501)
  - Watergate: Immunity, 1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 502)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, Against, 1973 November 9-27, December; (4 folders) (Box Box 502)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, Against, 1973 April-November 1-8, 1974 June-August; (8 folders) (Box Box 503)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, Against, 1974 January-May; (7 folders) (Box Box 504)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, For, 1973 November-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 505)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, For, 1973 October 26-31; (5 folders) (Box Box 506)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, For, 1973 October 23-26; (6 folders) (Box Box 507)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, For, 1973 May-October 22, 1974 May-August; (7 folders) (Box Box 508)
  - Watergate: Impeachment, For, 1974 January-April; (4 folders) (Box Box 509)
  - Watergate: Pardon, 1974 September 16-30, October-November; (3 folders) (Box Box 509)
  - Watergate: Pardon, 1974 September 3-13; (3 folders) (Box Box 510)
  - Watergate: Pension & Expenses of Nixon, 1974 September-November (Box Box 510)
  - Watergate: Resignation, 1974; (2 folders) (Box Box 510)
  - Welfare, 1973-1980 February-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 511)
  - Welfare, 1980 January, 1981-1982; (4 folders) (Box Box 512)
  - Welfare: Adoption & Foster Care, 1978-1982 (Box Box 512)
  - Welfare: Aid to Aging, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 512)
  - Welfare: Aid to Families with Dependent Children, 1973-1982 (Box Box 512)
  - Welfare: Catastrophic Health Insurance and Medical Assistance Reform Act (S. 2513 & S. 1416), 1973 (Box Box 513)
  - Welfare: Child Abuse, 1973-1982 (Box Box 513)
  - Welfare: Child Development - Day Care, 1974-1976 March-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 513)
  - Welfare: Child Development - Day Care, 1976 January-February, 1977-1981; (5 folders) (Box Box 514)
  - Welfare: Child Development - Day Care Amendment (S. 3617), 1972-1974 (Box Box 514)
  - Welfare: Legal Services, 1973-1974 (Box Box 515)
  - Welfare: Legislation, 1972-1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 515)
  - Welfare: Medicaid, 1974-1982; (3 folders) (Box Box 515)
  - Welfare: Medicare, 1974-1975; (2 folders) (Box Box 515)
  - Welfare: Medicare, 1976-1979 August-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 516)
  - Welfare: Medicare, 1979 January-July, 1980-1981; (6 folders) (Box Box 517)
  - Welfare: Medicare, 1982; (2 folders) (Box Box 518)
  - Welfare: National Health Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box Box 518)
  - Welfare: Nursing Homes, 1973-1979 (Box Box 518)
  - Welfare: Older Americans Comprehensive Services Amendments of 1973 (S. 50) (Box Box 518)
  - Welfare: Professional Standards Review Organizations, 1973-1980; (2 folders) (Box Box 518)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1974 August-December (Box Box 518)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1974 January-July, 1975; (6 folders) (Box Box 519)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1976, 1977 November-December; (7 folders) (Box Box 520)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1977 January-October; (6 folders) (Box Box 521)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1978-1979 July-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 522)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1979 January-June, 1980 May-June; (7 folders) (Box Box 523)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1980 January-April, 1981 October-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 524)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1981 May-September; (6 folders) (Box Box 525)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1981 January-April, 1982 April-December; (6 folders) (Box Box 526)
  - Welfare: Social Security, 1982 January-March; (2 folders) (Box Box 527)
  - Welfare: Social Security Amendment (Mondale S. 2528), 1973 (Box Box 527)
  - Welfare: Vista, 1974-1979 (Box Box 527)
  - Welfare: Vocational Rehabilitation, 1973-1981; (2 folders) (Box Box 527)
- Series III: Transitional Legislative Files
  - Administrative File - Beginning of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. Senatorial Career, 1965 November-1966 March (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Air & Water Pollution, 1965-1966 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Airport Bill of Senator Cotton (S. 3523), 1966 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Appalachia, 1964-1965 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Budget, 1966 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Capitol Restoration, 1966 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Civil Rights, 1965-1966, n.d.; (3 folders) (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Gathright Dam & James River, 1962-1965 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Humane Treatment of Animals (Humane Society Center - S. 1071), 1965 (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Memoranda, 1965, n.d. (Box Box 528)
  - Legislation: Memoranda, 1966; (4 folders) (Box Box 529)
  - Legislation: Minimum Wage & Poverty, 1965 (Box Box 529)
  - Legislation: Reapportionment, 1964-1966 (Box Box 529)
  - Legislation: Right-to-Work, 1965-1966, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 529)
  - Political: Miscellaneous Printed, 1964-1966 (Box Box 530)
  - Speech Drafts, 1966; (2 folders) (Box Box 530)